Denmark
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Denmark
2.1.1.1.6
Marist College
MMM
MMM
MMM
  Box 1178
- Denmark, 2.1.1.1.6
  - Tunnel under old entrance to Kronburg Castle, Helsingor, circa 1915; 19; 6000; 30; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Courtyard of Kronburg Castle, Helsingor, circa 1915; 20; 6001; 19; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Wall and canal of kronberg Castle, Helsingor, circa 1915; 21; 6002; 39; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Kronburg Castle, Helsingor, circa 1915; 22; 6034; 510; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Kronburg Castle, Helsingor, circa 1915; 23; 6035; 12; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Entrance to Kronburg Castle, Helsingor, circa 1915; 24; 6036; 5; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Flag battery, Kronburg Castle, Helsingor, circa 1915; 25; 6038; 9; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Parafel wall and flag battery, Kronburg Castle, Helsingor, circa 1915; 26; 6039; 10; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Kronburg Castle, Helsingor, circa 1915; 27; 6041; 602; 4x5 film (Box 1178)
  - St. Alban English Church, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 28; 6004; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Friege at Thorwaldsen's Church, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 29; 6006; 1; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Thorwalden's twelve disciples in interior of Fruekuk Church, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 30; 6007; 37; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Christ and the angels, Thorwalden's Church, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 31; 6008; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - The Tivoli entrance, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 32; 6009; 40; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Tivoli gardens, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 33; 6010; 28; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Casino in Tivoli, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 34; 6011; 27; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Bridge leaving to new part of Copenhagen, circa 1915; 35; 6012; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Staadrhown, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 36; 6014; 26; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Palace of King, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 37; 6016; 2; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Marble church, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 38; 6017; 415; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Vor Frelsers Kirke, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 39; 6018; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Entrance to Rosenburg Castle, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 40; 6020; 29; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Boulevard with modern apartment, houses in Copenhagen, circa 1915; 41; 60021; A; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Glyprorek, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 42; 6022; 22; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - City from tower in zoo, garden, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 43; 6023; 33; 5x7 (Box 1178)
  - Banana stand in Copenhagen, circa 1915; 44; 6025; 5; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Round Tower, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 45; 6026; 9; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Round Tower, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 46; 6027; 10; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Opera house, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 47; 6028; 12; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Street in Copenhagen, circa 1915; 48; 6029; 4x5 film (Box 1178)
  - Nyhavn, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 49; 6030; 13; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - New hotel(Bristol) in Copenhagen, circa 1915; 50; 6031; 4x5 film (Box 1178)
  - Children in front of Bourse, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 51; 6032; 14; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Royal guard, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 52; 6033; 508; 4x5 (Box 1178)
  - Shipping in Stockholm Canal, Copenhagen, circa 1915; 53; 6037; 4x5 film (Box 1178)
  - Turning trolley car in Copenhagen, circa 1915; 54; 6040; 4x5 film (Box 1178)